얘들아
이걸 봐, 정말 굉장해
Check it out, this is unbelievable!
조이가 4분째 숨을 참고 있어
Joey's been holding his breath
for almost four minutes.
You trying to kill me?
사람 잡으려고 작정했냐?
- 피비, 뭐 하나 물어볼게
- 뭔데?
-I want to ask you something.
-What?
나 이사 가야 하는데
넌 정말 예쁘잖아
Since I'm moving out,
and you're so beautiful...
how about I move in with you?
너희 집으로 들어가도 될까?
그럼 나도 좋지만
드니스는 어떡하고?
That would be great,
but what do we do about Denise?
- 드니스가 누군데?
- 내 룸메이트
-Who's Denise?
-My roommate.
룸메이트가 있었어?
Your roommate?
Yes, Denise. Denise!
그래, 드니스! 드니스!
우리한테 숨긴 이유가 뭐야?
드니스라니, 걔 예쁘냐?
What is with the secrecy, Phoebe?
What about Denise? She cute?
어떻게 그걸 아무도
모를 수가 있지?
How can you have a roommate
that we don't know about?
너희가 내 말을 듣기나 했어?
맨날 얘기했잖아, 드니스!
Because you never listen
to what I say.
I talk about her all the time.
Denise!
레이첼, 생각해보니까
우리 집도 방이 하나 남아
I'm gonna have an extra room
over at my place.
그렇구나
우리 집으로 들어와
-That's true.
-Move in with me.
We can stay up late talking,
and watch movies.
재미있을 거야, 늦게까지
얘기도 하고 영화도 보고
'알몸 목요일'은 알고 있지?
You know about
naked Thursdays, right?
그냥 다른 데 알아볼게
Yeah, yeah. I think
I'll find my own place.
야, 임마
Hey! I thought naked Thursdays
was just our thing, man.
알몸 목요일은
우리만의 행사잖아
The One With Ross' Denial
- 여기 있었네
- 왔어?
아직 부부라니까
레이첼이 뭐래?
What did Rachel say when you told her
you were still married to her?
그거?
Oh, that.
잘 넘어갔어
She took it really well.
- 얘기 안 했구나
- 그래
-You didn't tell her, did you?
-No.
Because you're in love with her.
당연히 안 했겠지
레이첼을 사랑하니까
I am not in love with her. She was
upset about having to move out.
사랑하는 게 아냐
집 나가는 것 때문에
마음이 상해있는데
거기다 대고 어떻게
그런 얘기까지 하겠어
If she knew we were still married,
she'd have been more upset.
그냥 위로만 해줬지
친구로서
So I comforted her.
As a friend.
You "comforted her"?
위로라니 무슨 뜻이야?
살짝 안아준 것 뿐이야
Nothing.
I just gave her a hug.
아하! 전형적인
사랑의 표현이지
A classic sign of love,
the hug.
우정의 표현이기도 해
It's also a sign of friendship.
네 경우엔 아냐
이 물러터진 연애꾼아!
Not in your case, "Lovey Loverson."
It was a hug. Okay?
그냥 포옹이었다니까
알겠어? 단순한 포옹
A simple hug.
I was a friend being a friend
to a friend.
친구가 친구한테
친구 역할을 한 거라고
그 '친구' 더 동원해봐
Use the word "friend" more.
대답해봐, 레이첼
머리 냄새 안 맡았어?
Did you, or did you not,
smell her hair?
머리 냄새를 맡아?
Smell her hair?
What if I did?
맡았으면 그게 뭐
여자는 페로몬의 90%가
머리꼭대기에서 나와
Ninety percent of a woman's
pheromones come out of her head.
그래서 남자보다 키가 작지
That's why women are shorter.
So that men will fall in love
when they hug them.
남자가 여자를 안으면
사랑에 빠지는 거야
Come on, Ross,
you're a scientist.
과학자가 그것도 몰라?
친구로서 안아준 것 뿐이야
I was hugging her as a friend.
머리숱이 많으니까 내 얼굴에
닿을 수밖에 없지, 그 냄새는...
It's not my fault
her hair got in my face.
She's got a lot of it,
and it smells all... all...
꼭 코코넛 같더라
coconutty.
What? It doesn't mean
I have feelings for Rachel.
왜? 난 레이첼이 아니라
코코넛 좋아하면 안 돼?
Maybe it means
I have feelings for coconuts.
그래, 어쨌든 좋은데 조심해
레이첼 생각은 다르니까
Okay, but be careful. Rachel's not
in the same place you are.
그 '생각'이 '사랑'을 뜻한다면
레이첼 '생각'도 나랑 같아
If the place you're
referring to is being in love...
she is in the same place as me,
because I am not in that place.
내 '생각'도 그렇지 않으니까
I didn't understand that.
그 말은 못 알아듣겠다
은밀한 사랑의 언어를
이해하긴 힘들지
Maybe that's because you were
speaking the secret language of love.
누가 전화했더라
-A guy just called for you.
-Who was it?
누군데?
I don't know. How about
"Thanks for taking the message"?
알 게 뭐야
전해준 건 안 고맙냐? 젠장
네가 들어오면
레이첼 방이 비잖아
When you move in...
Rachel's room will be empty.
Let's talk about what to do with it.
그 방 어떻게 할지 얘기할까?
- 좋아
- 그래
I think we should have
a beautiful guest room...
근사한 객실을 만드는 게 어때?
with a mahogany sleigh bed and
bedside tables with fresh flowers.
마호가니 침대 옆엔 항상
싱싱한 꽃을 꽂아두는 거야
뚜껑 달린 책상에 카드를 두면
모두들 감사인사를 남기겠지?
And comment cards so people could
tell us how great their stay was.
I really haven't
thought about it that much.
글쎄, 아직 생각을
많이 해본 건 아냐
Well, I like that idea... obviously.
괜찮은 거 같다, 진짜로
I was thinking maybe...
maybe it could be a game room.
난 오락실을 만들면
어떨까 하는데
구식 아케이드게임 있잖아
You can buy old arcade games, like
Space lnvaders and Asteroids...
스페이스 인베이더나
애스터로이드 같은 건
for $200. The real ones.
The big, big, big ones!
2백 달러면 대따
큰 걸 살 수 있어
No.
싫어
You mean "No" as in:
방금 그 말은 이것도
괜찮은 아이디어지만
"What an interesting idea. Let's
discuss it before we reject it."
상의를 해보자는 뜻이겠지?
I'm sorry.
미안해, 좋아
괜찮은 생각이다
상의해보자
Interesting idea. But no.
난 싫어
So that's it?
그게 끝이야?
I just don't think arcade games
go in a beautiful guest room...
품위 있는 객실에는
아케이드게임기가 아니라
filled with antiques.
고풍스런 가구가 어울리잖아
그러니까 최고 구닥다리
애스터로이드가 딱이지
Which is why Asteroids is
perfect. It's the oldest game.
What's wrong with
a beautiful guest room?
객실을 반대하는 이유가 뭐야?
내가 왜 객실을 반대하겠어
우리가 아는 사람들은 모두...
I'm not against it.
Especially since everybody we know
lives about 30 seconds away.
30초 거리에 살고 있는데
Are you mocking me?
빈정대는 거야?
아니, 너랑 우아한 객실을
빈정댈 순 없지요
No, I'm not mocking you
or your beautiful guest room.
왜 그래?
모니카랑 좀 다퉜어
Monica and l
had a stupid fight.
You're still moving in together,
right? My ad came out today.
그래도 집은 옮길 거지?
오늘 신문에 광고 냈어
"Wanted: Female roommate,
nonsmoker, nonugly."
'여성 룸메이트 구함
흡연자 및 추녀 사절'
- 좋다, 야
- 그렇지?
Nice.
I figured it'd be more interesting
to have a female roommate.
너랑은 살아봤으니까
여자 룸메이트도 좋을 것 같아
Someone I could learn from.
Someone who's different than me.
뭔가 배울 게 있는 사람
나랑은 다른 사람
And what's more different than me,
a guy who's not 19...
누가 더 나랑 다를까?
19살이 아닌 남자랑
19살인 여자랑
than a girl who is 19?
머리는 장식품이 아냐, 친구
Not just a hatrack, my friend.
Phoebe, I have to ask you..
- 피비, 하나만 물어보자
- 쉿! 나 지금 바빠
I'm swamped right now.
You're just staring into space.
그냥 허공만 바라보고 있잖아
I'm trying to move that pencil.
저 연필을 움직일 거야
-This one?
-lt worked!
- 이거?
- 성공이다!
집 구하는 게
보통일이 아니다
Phoebe, this whole apartment thing
is a nightmare.
내 수준에 맞는다 싶으면
꼭 변태 같은 룸메이트가 있어
Anything I can afford comes with
a roommate who is a freak. Look.
이걸 봐
"Wanted: Female roommate,
nonsmoker, nonugly."
'여성 룸메이트 구함
흡연자 및 추녀 사절'
That's probably some 12-year-old kid
trying to get girls to call.
여자친구를 찾는
12살짜리 앤가 보다
이렇게 빈방 구하기가
힘들어서야 원
There's nothing. This city is full.
Wait! Look at this!
잠깐, 여길 봐
"Two bedroom, two bath. Must be
nonsmoker. Satan worshipers okay."
'침실 둘, 욕실 둘, 흡연자 사절
사탄숭배자 환영'
Yeah, but it's on the ground floor.
저런, 1층이라 안 되겠다
- 얘들아
- 어서 와
-Rach, you still looking for a place?
-Yeah, why?
레이첼, 아직 집 못 구했니?
- 그래, 왜?
- 다행이다
박물관의 워렌이라는 친구가
2년 정도 발굴작업 나간대
This guy, Warren, from the museum
is going on a dig for two years.
집도 아주 괜찮은데
세를 주고 싶다네
He's got this great place he needs
to sublet. You interested?
관심 있어?
너무 잘됐다
Great! I'd love to live at Warren's.
I love Warren!
나 워렌 집에서 살래
나 워렌 좋아해
잠깐, 내 나체사진
달라던 친구 아냐?
Oh, wait. Is he the guy that asked you
for naked pictures of me?
That doesn't matter,
he won't be there!
괜찮아, 떠날 건데 뭐
고마워
-Thank you!
-Don't thank me.
나한테 고마워할 거 없어
Thank the volcano that erupted
thousands of years ago...
수천 년 전에 한 문명을
완전히 멸망시키고
killing, but perfectly preserving,
an entire civilization.
그걸 완벽하게 보존시킨
화산 덕분이니까
Here's Warren's number.
이게 워렌 연락처야
잘됐다, 당장 전화해야지
This is great. I'm gonna
call him right now! Thank you!
- 그래
- 고마워
됐어, 빨리 전화해
Okay, you go call him.
I saw it.
다 봤어
What are you talking about?
무슨 소린지 모르겠는데?
네가 이미 알면서도
인정하지 않는 사실
I'm talking about what you already
know but won't admit.
넌 레이첼을
'재차' 사랑하게 됐어
You love her again. You re-love her.
I do not re-love her.
난 레이첼을
'재차' 사랑하지 않아
끝까지 인정을 안 하시네
I can't believe
you won't just admit it.
어쨌든 바보짓이나 하지 마
Promise me
you won't do anything stupid.
지금은 그냥 친구야
내가 무슨 바보짓을 하겠어
We're just friends now.
Why would I do anything stupid?
그 아파트 벌써 나갔데
되는 일이 없다니까
The apartment
is already subletted.
It's hopeless.
I'll never find anything.
이러다 길거리에 나앉겠어
Live with me.
그럼 우리 집으로 와
-What?
-What?!
- 뭐?
What?
뭐?
Are you serious?
- 어머, 진심이야?
- 응...
너랑 같이 살면 좋지
고마워서 어떡하니
I would love to live with you.
That's great. Thank you.
도움이 됐다면 내가 기쁘지
I'm just glad I could help you out.
두 사람 참 좋겠구나
전혀 바보 같지 않은 짓이다
Wow, I'm so happy for you guys.
This is so, so, not stupid.
로스, 이게 무슨 뜻인지 아니?
졸지에 떠돌이가 될 뻔했는데
Ross, you have no idea
what this means to me.
I was gonna be homeless.
You just saved me. You're my hero.
네가 날 구했어
넌 내 영웅이야
Hero? I don't know.
Well, all right.
영웅이라니
내가 무슨... 알았어
모니카한테 가서
오빠 칭찬 좀 해줘야겠다
I have to go tell Monica
what a wonderful brother she has.
Oh, please.
왜 이래...
또 야단칠 거지?
You're gonna say things now,
aren't you?
No. No, I won't.
아니, 야단은 무슨
But I should tell you this.
하지만 이건 알아둬
The same thing happened to my
roommate, Denise.
내 룸메이트 드니스한테도
똑같은 일이 있었어
She moved in with a guy
who was secretly married to her.
걔 몰래 혼인신고를 한
남자랑 같이 살았는데
그 남자도 자기 감정을 극구
부인했었지, 결국은 깨졌어
He said he didn't love her, but he
really did. And it just blew up.
그래서 나랑 살게 된 거야
And that's how she ended up
living with me.
Okay, that's a lie.
그래, 뻥이다
-You don't have a roommate.
-Denise!
넌 룸메이트 없어
드니스!
No one ever listens to me!
내 말은 개소리로 들어!
- 나야
- 그래
아까 일은 미안해
나 오락실 필요 없어
Listen, I'm sorry about before.
I don't need a game room.
I only played those games because I
couldn't get girls. Now I can get..
전엔 여자가 궁해서
게임만 했는데
이젠 안 궁하잖아
Now I have you.
자기가 있으니까
No, not that I think I have you...
그렇다고 자기가
내 거라든지
소유물이라고
생각한 적은 없어
or think of you as property
in any sort of way. I see women....
- 모름지기 여성이란...
- 그만해, 챈들러
Stop it, Chandler.
I'm sorry too.
나도 미안해
-Really?
-Yeah. Oh, yes.
- 정말?
- 그래
그럼
꼭 객실이 아니라도 돼
We can think of something
to do with the room together.
함께 차분히 생각해보자
Great idea. We can easily think of
a way for us both to enjoy the room.
좋지, 둘 다 만족할 만한
방법이 분명 있을 거야
Totally.
물론이지
-We don't have to decide now.
-Good.
- 당장 결정할 건 없잖아
- 그럼
먼저 거실을 어떻게
바꿀지나 생각해보자
Let's think about changes
we can make in the living room.
Changes?
바꿔?
We'll have to move some
furniture to make room for my chair.
내 의자 갖다 놓으려면
가구 배치를 바꿔야지
You're bringing the Barcalounger
over here?
그 의자를 가져오겠다고?
Is that a problem?
무슨 문제 있어?
저기...
It's just that they're a set
and should stay together.
그건 세트니까
같이 두는 게 좋잖아
그럼 두 개 다 가져오지 뭐
That's cool.
I'll bring them both over.
You're taking them away
from their home.
의자들에겐 저 집이 고향이야
알았다, 내 물건은 하나도
들이지 말라는 뜻이지?
I get it. I get nothing. Nothing
here is mine. Everything is yours.
I'll get up in the morning, put on
your clothes and go off to work!
아침에 일어나면 네 옷 입고
룰루랄라 출근할게
Yeah, that's it. Everything will be mine.
Nothing will be yours.
좋아, 알았어
그렇게 하자
이 집엔 내 물건만 있어야 돼
내 말이 그 말이야
왜 이래, 의자 얘기잖아
I'm talking about the Barcalounger.
It doesn't match.
Where will it go?
어울리지도 않는 걸
어디다 두냐고
오락실에!
In the game room!
It is not my fault your
chairs are incredibly ugly.
그 의자가 흉물단지로
생겨먹은 건 내 탓이 아냐
That's fine.
됐어, 알았다고
안 가져오면 되잖아
I won't bring the chairs.
I won't bring anything!
아무 것도 안 가져와
나도 이 퀘퀘한 할머니 집
분위기 망치고 싶지 않아!
I wouldn't want to ruin the ambiance
over here at grandma's place!
Everything on your application
looks really good.
신청서는 별 문제가 없군요
참, 마지막으로 하나만 묻죠
Just one last question.
Will your friends be over here,
partying and hanging out?
친구들 불러서 파티하고
노는 거 좋아하세요?
걱정 마세요
난 파티광 아니니까
Don't worry.
I'm not a party girl.
어허!
그렇게 덥석 대답하지 말고
Don't just be blurting stuff out.
I want you to really think
about your answers.
신중히 생각한 후 답변하세요
Call off the roommate search.
Hi. I'll be living here.
룸메이트 찾는 거 포기해라
안녕하세요? 제가 살 겁니다
Ignore him. He's just some
guy who wants the apartment.
못 들은 걸로 하세요, 이 집에
들어오려고 안달 난 친구니까
But he's not going to get it.
하여간 꿈은 야무져요
샤워커튼은 왜 뗐냐?
You took down the shower curtain?
That thing was a hazard!
위험한 물건이야
모름지기 안전이 우선이죠
I'm very safety conscious.
나 왔어
I was just clearing some space
for your stuff.
그래, 몇 군데 치우고 있었어
고마워
Thanks.
근데 모니카랑 챈들러가 크게
싸우고 같이 사는 거 취소했대
But listen, Monica and Chandler had a
big fight and they're not moving in.
What do you mean, not moving in?
They're still moving in, right?
취소하다니 무슨 말이야
그냥 말로만 그런 거지?
No, they just had a big blowout
over what to do with my room.
아니, 내 방을 어떻게 할까
궁리하다 대판 붙었나봐
그 바보 같은 방 때문에?
Over a stupid room?
I feel kind of bad for them, but now
I don't have to move in here!
두 사람 생각하면 안됐지만
난 이제 집 안 옮겨도 되잖아
맞아, 그 부분은 잘된 일이다
Oh, no. Yeah, that part's great.
What's all this
about you guys fighting?
중뿔났다고 싸우고 난리야?
Is this really over a room?
방 하나 때문에?
정말 한심스럽다
That is so silly.
-We can handle this.
-Apparently not.
우리끼리 해결할 수 있어
그럼 오죽 좋겠냐만
And I can't stand by and watch
two people I care about so much...
내가 아끼는 두 사람이
그따위 한심한 이유로
상처받는 걸 앉아서
구경만 할 순 없어요
be hurt by something
that is so silly.
한심한 작태들은 그만둬
Enough of the silliness.
Tell her to stop being silly.
한심한 작태를 누가 보이는데
됐어, 그만해
Two very good points.
둘 다 좋은 지적이야
얘들아
I've known you both a long time.
난 너희들을
오래 전부터 알았지만
And I've never seen either of you
one-millionth as happy...
두 사람이 요즘처럼 행복해하는
모습은 한 번도 본 적이 없어
as you've been
since you got together.
그런데 겨우 방 하나 때문에
그걸 몽땅 날려버린다?
Do you really want
to throw that all away over a room?
That is so silly.
정말 한심한 짓이야
What's more important, love...
뭐가 더 중요하겠니
사랑과 한심한 짓 중에서
or silliness?
Well, we are fond of the silliness.
우린 한심한 짓도 좋아하지만
But we also have a soft spot
for the love.
사랑에 대해서도
애착을 갖고 있지
-Love is the best medicine.
-That's "laughter."
- 사랑이 명약이야
- 웃음이 명약이지
- 요점이 뭐야?
- 나도 몰라
-Why do you do it?
-I don't know.
자, 그만들 해
Now, Chandler, you want
to live with Monica, right?
챈들러, 모니카랑
살고 싶은 거 맞지?
그래
Yeah, I do.
너도 챈들러랑 살고 싶지?
And, Mon, you want
to live with Chandler?
Yes.
그래
좋아, 뉴욕에선 구두계약도
그 효력이 발생한다!
A verbal contract is binding
in the state of New York!
So I understand you're
looking for a place?
방을 구한다면서?
No, I'm staying put.
아뇨, 계속 살게 됐어요
I was going to offer you
my apartment.
우리 집에 들어오라고
할 생각이었는데
왜요? 어디 가요?
Why? Where you going?
I don't know.
몰라
- 안녕, 레이첼
- 어서 와
You won't believe it.
믿어지지 않겠지만
Monica and Chandler
are moving in again.
모니카랑 챈들러가
다시 합치기로 했어
굉장한 소식이지?
두 사람한테는, 안 그래?
That's great news, right?
I mean, for them, right?
좋은 쪽으로 생각하면
우린 다시 룸메이트가 되잖아
But on the bright side,
we get to be roommates again.
그래, 바로 그거 말인데...
Yeah. You know, about that....
날 들어오라고 한 건
정말 고마운 일이지만
I really appreciate your offer
to let me move in and everything...
but don't you think
it'll be weird?
좀 이상하지 않을까?
왜?
Why? Why would it....
Why would it be weird?
그게 왜...
뭐가 이상한데?
알잖아, 너랑 나니까
Well, you know,
because of us.
사귀던 사이잖아
Because of our history.
- 말도 안 돼
- 그래?
No!
No, no!
안 되고말고
It would only be weird
if we were still in "that place."
옛날 같은 감정이라면
이상할 수도 있겠지만...
너 그때랑 똑같아?
Are you still in that place?
-No, not at all.
-Good. Me neither.
- 아니, 천만에
- 잘됐다, 나도 그러니까
So it's not a problem.
그럼 문제될 거 없잖아
친구끼리 룸메이트가
되는 것 뿐이야
We're just two friends
who happen to be roommates.
Okay, but eventually
you and I will be dating.
하지만 결국 우린
데이트를 하게 될 텐데
Really? We are?
정말 그럴까?
Yeah. I'll have a boyfriend
and you'll have a girlfriend.
그래, 나도 남자를 만날 거고
너도 여자를 만날 거고
오! 그렇게 되면 좋지
That'd be great.
But if you think it'll be okay,
we'll just work out a system.
너만 괜찮다면 규칙을 정하자
It'll be like in college.
I'll hang a sign on the door:
대학 때처럼 문에다
팻말을 걸어두는 거야
'이따 와, 오늘 봉 잡았다'
"Come back later.
I'm getting lucky."
Yeah, I didn't think of that.
그 생각은 미처 못했다
So are you sure about
this whole moving-in thing?
너희들 진짜 같이 살 거야?
이런 인륜지 대사를
서둘러선 안 되지
It's a really big step.
And what's the rush?
오빠 진짜 웃긴다
That's very funny.
He's being silly because
he knows we enjoy the silliness.
우리가 한심한 짓 좋아한다고
한심하게 나오는 거야
이건 심각한 얘기야
잘 생각해봐
No, I'm serious.
Think about it. You move in.
챈들러가 들어오면
한심한 오락실 문제로 싸움이
시작되고 결국 헤어지게 돼
You start fighting over game rooms.
Next thing you know, you break up.
It was just a stupid fight
about a room.
오빠 말이 맞았어, 방 때문에
싸운 건 정말 한심한 짓이야
세상에 한심한 싸움은 없어
There are no stupid fights!
단순히 방 문제가 아니라
This isn't about the room.
This is about
what the room represents.
방이 상징하는 바가 문제야
유감이지만 이 방이
너희를 파멸시킬 거야
And unfortunately,
this room could destroy you!
그런 걱정은 안 해
-I'm not so worried.
-Me neither.
그래, 나도
Fine. It's your life!
좋다, 너희 인생이니까
깨지는 걸 보고 싶진 않지만
I just don't want
to see you break up.
두 사람이 합치면
그런 사태가 발생해
Which you will do
if you move in together.
But if that's what you want,
there's nothing I can do.
그걸 원한다면
나도 별수가 없지
Don't do it!
하지 마!
-You still want to move in together?
-Of course.
- 그래도 같이 살 거지?
- 물론
Ross didn't scare you?
그 말 듣고도 괜찮아?
쟤랑은 죽어도 같이 안 산다
Scared me out of wanting
to live with him.
-I gotta show you something.
-Okay.
- 보여줄 게 있어
- 그래
세상에, 네모인간이
살해당했군
Oh, my God!
Someone's killed Square Man!
네 안락의자 여기다 놓자
The Barcalounger can go here.
You can see the TV, and it's still
walking distance to the kitchen.
여기서 TV도 볼 수 있고
동시에 주방하고도 가깝고
이렇게 고마울 데가
Oh, that's so sweet.
I want to show you
something too.
- 나도 보여줄 게 있어
- 좋아
'차선합류'라고 적힌
커다란 표지판 알지?
You know those big road signs
that say "merge"?
내가 생각한 건데
I thought we could get one of those
signs and hang it over our bed.
그걸 하나 뜯어다가
침대 머리맡에 달자고
다시 말해 너랑 내가...
Because that's you and I together.
"Merge!"
'차선합류'
- 어머, 근사하겠다
- 진짜?
-I love that!
-Really?
'아뇨'
"No!"
내 침대 속의 그대
어떻게 올라왔나요
I found you in my bed
How'd you wind up there?
그대는 수수께끼
새까만 곱슬머리
You are a mystery
Little black curly hair
새까만 곱슬머리
Little black, little black,
little black
새까만, 새까만, 새까만
새까만, 새까만 곱슬머리
Little black curly hair
감사합니다
제 공연일정을 E메일로
받아보고 싶은 분은
If you want to receive e-mails
about my upcoming shows...
컴퓨터 하나 사게
돈 좀 기부하세요
please give me money
so I can buy a computer.
다른 애들은?
Where are the other guys?
모니카랑 챈들러는
지금 정신이 없고
Well, Monica and Chandler
are occupied.
-Fighting?
-The other thing.
- 싸우느라?
- 아니, 다른 일로
It's great they worked things out.
잘 해결돼서 정말 다행이야
그래, 결국 안 깨지고 말았어
There's no breaking them up,
is there?
집 열쇠 있지?
하나 더 만들어 올게
Can I borrow the key to your house
so I can go make a copy?
그래, 여기
-Here.
-Thank you.
고마워
후회 안 하지? 일단 열쇠
만들면 돌이킬 수 없는데
Are you sure? Once I make
a copy, there's no turning back.
Yeah, I'm sure. Now get out
of here before I change my mind.
그럼, 마음 변하기 전에
빨리 갔다 와
로스
레이첼하고 사는 게
정말 좋은 생각일까?
You think moving in
with Rachel is a good idea?
나도 오락가락해
I've been back and forth.
그럼 돌아가, 알았어?
Well, maybe you should go back.
레이첼이 들어가면
She moves in,
and before you know it...
너도 모르는 사이에
다시 엮이게 된다고
you're right where you don't
want to be, back together.
아닐 거야, 벌써 다른 남자
만날 생각을 하고 있던데?
I don't think so. She's already
talking about dating other guys.
That's not going to work out.
She'll come home all weepy...
그게 잘도 되겠다
어느 날 울상을 하고
들어오면 넌 이러겠지
and you'll be telling her, "Oh,
that's okay. You'll find someone."
'진정해, 남자는 또 있어'
그리고 짠!
And then, bam! She finds you!
그게 바로 너야
맞아, 그럴지도 모르지
Maybe you're right.
장담하지만 레이첼은
널 다시 좋아하게 될 거야
Ross, she is definitely
gonna fall in love with you again.
그걸 바라냐?
Is that what you want?
그걸 바라냐고?
Is that what I want?
당연하지
Yes.
저기 온다
넌 구경이나 하고 있어
Here she comes. I'm gonna
make your life much easier.
The place was closed,
so I'll copy it later.
문 닫아서 다음에
만들어야겠다
그럴 게 아니라
Or not.
Why don't you move in with me?
레이첼, 우리 집으로
들어오는 게 어때?
워! 워! 조이...
Whoa, Joey!
아냐, 난 괜찮아
Look, I know I scared you with
that whole naked-Thursdays thing...
알몸 목요일 때문에
네가 좀 놀랐나본데
but we don't have to do that.
그런 건 안 해도 돼
It would be easier
to move across the hall.
하긴 복도 건너편으로
이사하는 게 훨씬 편하지
Unless you're thinking about
naked Wednesdays.
혹시 알몸 수요일을
생각하는 건 아니지?
Thursday's clearly not good for you.
Pick a day!
그렇게 목요일이 싫다면
아무 날이나 고르렴
- 어서 와요
- 안녕하세요
Come on in.
Thanks for coming back.
들어오세요
다시 와줘서 고마워요
There's a lot of people
interested in the room.
관심 가진 사람이
아주 많았는데
But I've narrowed it down,
and you're one of the finalists.
최종후보 명단에
그쪽도 올라갔어요
-Great!
-Before I decide...
- 잘됐네요
- 결정을 내리기 전에
I want to be sure
our personalities match.
서로 성격이 잘 맞는지
확인을 해봐야겠어요
간단한 테스트를 하죠
So I made up a little test.
내가 어떤 단어를 말하면 제일
먼저 떠오르는 단어를 말해요
I'll say a word, and you say
the first thing that comes to mind.
-I can do that.
-Okay, here we go.
- 그 정도야 뭐
- 자, 그럼 시작하죠
-Pillow.
-Fight.
- 베개
- 싸움
Very good.
잘하시네
좋아요
"G."
- G...
- 스트링?
-String?
-Excellent!
절묘합니다
어디 보자
Doggy.
강아지...
-Kitten?
-Sorry!
- 고양이?
- 오! 안타깝군요
So close, though. Bye-bye!
거의 정답이었는데
할 수 없죠, 잘 가요